http://www.rivercruises.net/privacy-policy

Skip to content
See Our New 2021 Brochure...
Agent Login
Client Login
Travel Updates...
Our Fleet
M/Y Adriatic PrestigeMS Swiss RubyM/S VivienneM/S AuroraM/S CrucevitaM/S FarahM/S Fiji PrincessM/S Moonlight SonataMV Mekong Prestige II
Escorted ToursBlogSPECIALS!
TRAVEL UPDATES
Privacy Policy
Luxurious, intimate and unforgetable,
Valueworldcruises.com is owned and operated by Value World Tours Incorporated. The following describes the privacy policy (as amended or otherwise changed from time to time, the “Privacy Policy”) applicable to the services available through the valueworldcruises.com web site (the “Site”) from valueworldcruises.com. Certain services which you may access on the Site are provided by our third party partners, and protection of your information relating to such services will be governed by the privacy policy of such third party (see “Sharing Your Personal Data-Certain Services,” below). By visiting the Site, you are consenting to the collection, use, disclosure and processing of your personal data described in this Privacy Policy.
On occasion Value World Tours may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the law, our Personal Data collection and use practices, the features of our Site, or advances in technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your Personal Data, those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. Value World Tours will also prominently post such material changes prior to implementing the change.
Our Commitment to Your Privacy
Value World Tours complies with the framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data. In particular, with respect to personally identifiable data obtained about: (i) customers and visitors to this Site; (ii) suppliers, business partners, customers, and website visitors; and (iii) employees of our affiliates and partners. Customer Data is handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and any questions about such data should be directed to us as specified in the “How to Contact Us” section below.
We value your trust in us and will work hard to earn your confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to your friends and family.
Information We Collect
We collect personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”) about you that you provide to us while using the Site. Personal Data includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name, address, phone number, credit card number or e-mail address. We also collect non-personally identifiable information, which may be linked to your Personal Data, including your log-in name, IP address, search preferences related to specific searches, and bids through our valueworldcruises.com cookies.
Protecting Your Personal Data
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of Personal Data, we will employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies.
If you purchase certain services, such as cruise reservations or airline tickets, for other travelers, we will collect the names of the other travelers. You must make sure that you have the right to provide such information. By providing any Personal Data of another traveler, you represent that you have all necessary authority and/or have obtained all necessary consents from such person to enable us to collect, use and disclose such Personal Data as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Personal Data of other travelers is collected only for the purpose of providing such other travelers’ names to the appropriate travel supplier, such as the vessel or the airline on which travel will occur.
How We Use the Information We Collect
We use Personal Data to provide you with the products and services from our Site, to build features that will make the services available on the Site easier to use, and to contact you about these services. This includes faster purchase requests, better customer support and timely notice of new services and special offers.
From time to time, valueworldcruises.com may contact you to request feedback on your experience using the Site, to assist us in improving the Site, or to offer special savings or promotions to you, as a Site user. If you would prefer not to receive notices of special savings or promotions, you may simply opt-out from receiving them by replying to Value World Tours by using the hyperlink provided in these notices.
Sharing Your Personal Data
Value World Tours does not share your Personal Data, except as disclosed in this statement or unless we receive your consent. Value World Tours may share your Personal Data with its subsidiaries and with third parties as described in the categories below:
Certain Services: In order to provide you with certain services, we may share your Personal Data with our third party partners, or require that you transact directly with a third party partner. Third party partners consist of companies with which Value World Tours has contracted in order to provide you with services or products featured on our Site, such as cruise reservations, hotel accommodation, and airlines tickets.
External Service Providers: When you use the Value World Tours’ Site to purchase an airline ticket, reserve a cruise cabin, book a hotel room or to take advantage of any of our other products and services (including travel insurance and destination attractions), we provide Personal Data to the airline, cruise line, hotel, travel agency or other involved third-party.
Advertisements, Marketing Material and Other Offers: Unless you tell us that you do not want to receive these offers, Value World Tours may occasionally send advertisements, marketing material or other offers that we think might be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive these advertisements, marketing material or other offers, please let us know to unsubscribe you.
Compliance with Law and Other Disclosures: Value World Tours reserves the right to release Personal Data in order to comply with applicable law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our the Site. We may also release Personal Data to enforce or apply the terms and conditions applicable to our products and services, protect us or others against fraudulent or inappropriate activities, or otherwise protect the rights, property or safety of priceline.com, our affiliated companies, our customers, or others.
Our Policy Concerning Cookies
To serve you faster and with better quality, we use “cookie” technology and also allow third parties to use cookies on our Site. Cookies are small bits of code, usually stored on a user’s computer hard drive, which enable a web site to “personalize” itself for each user by remembering information about the user’s visit to the web site.
As described in more detail below, valueworldcruises.com.net cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience on our web site.
You can also delete all cookies that are already on your computer’s hard drive by searching for files with “cookie” in it. This action could affect your subsequent visits to certain web sites, including the valueworldcruises.com web site, by requiring that, for example, you enter you login name when you return to that web site.
To learn more about cookies, you can link to the following third-party web sites: http://www.cookiecentral.com, http://www.w3.org/, or http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie. These links are provided for your information only. Value World Tours is not affiliated with any of these third-party sites and does not make any representations or warranties about the information they contain.
How You Can Access or Change Your Personally-Identifying Information
Value World Tours understands that you may want to change, access or delete your Personal Data. You may do so by accessing your profile. To protect your privacy and security, we will verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your personally-identifying information. Any request to access your personally-identifying information will be answered in less than 30 days.
Message Boards & Photo Galleries
We may offer message boards and photo galleries for our customers’ enjoyment. As we are sure you are aware, anything you post online is available for the world to see. We make no representations and undertake no obligations as to information you voluntarily post. By posting a message on our site or sending in photos for our photo gallery, you understand it becomes public domain and therefore may be used by Value World Tours for marketing purposes without any compensation required to be paid to you.
California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits those customers that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of your personal information to other parties for their direct marketing purposes.To make such a request, please send an email to value@valueworldcruises.com or write to us at:Value World Tours, 17220 Newhope Street # 203, Fountain Valley, CA 92708.
Other Information and Governing Law
We reserve the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any legal investigation.
This policy is governed by the laws of the State of California.
A Special Note About Children
Persons under the age of 18 are not eligible to use any services on our site.
How to Contact Us
Should you have any questions, concerns or comments, please contact us. Value World Tours Incorporated is located at 17220 Newhope Street # 203, Fountain Valley, CA 92708.
Value InfoAbout UsContact UsCorporateSite MapPrivacy Policy
Travel With Value
Adriatic
Europe
Asia
Egypt
Fiji
Value Resources
Value World Tours, Inc. • 17220 Newhope Street, Suite 203 • Fountain Valley, CA 92708 •
(800) 795-1633
All Rights Reserved. Copyright 2020 © Value World Tours, Inc.
M/Y Adriatic PrestigeMS Swiss RubyM/S VivienneM/S AuroraM/S CrucevitaM/S FarahM/S Fiji PrincessM/S Moonlight SonataMV Mekong Prestige II
Escorted ToursBlogSPECIALS!WooCommerce not Found
Newsletter
See Our New 2021 Brochure...
Agent Login
Book now
